Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Corporate Records, 206870
  - M.F.C. Corp, 213022
    - Lawsuit, 1992; 213026 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Minute Book, 1949-1964; 213027 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Stock Book, 1949-1950; 213028 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - M. Little Lumber Co., 213325
    - Various Documents, n.d.; 213326 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Madison Ave- 36th Street Corp., 213327
    - Ledgers, 1947-1954; 213331 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Accounts Payable, 1947-1952; 213333 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Cash Book, 1947-1954; 213335 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Journal, 1947-1954; 213337 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Ledger Book (I), 1947-1955; 213341 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Ledger Book (II), 1947-1955; 213344 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Ledger Book, 1952; 213346 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Ledgers, 1952-1958; 213348 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Transfer Balances, 1952-1954; 213350 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Cash Book and General Journal, 1955-1958; 213351 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Ledger Book, 1955-1958; 213352 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Federal Tax Report, 213353 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Federal Tax Return, 1947-1953; 213354 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Balance Sheet and Operating Statement, 1948; 216471 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Income Tax Return, 1954-1959; 213355 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - State Tax Returns, 1948-1959; 213356 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - New York City Taxes, 1948-1954; 213357 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - New York State Reports, 1947-1954; 213359 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - FOAB and Withholding Tax Reports, 1947-1952; 213358 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - N.Y. State Disability Insurance Tax Return, 213362 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Taxes- N.Y. City Real Estate Taxes and Water Meter Taxes, 213365 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Working Papers, 1947-1948; 213367 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Working Papers, 1948; 213368 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Working Papers, 1949; 213371 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Working Papers, 1949; 213373 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Working Papers, 1950; 213375 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Working Papers, 1951; 213376 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Working Papers, 1952; 213377 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Payroll Summeries, 213380 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Working Papers, 1953; 213381 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Working Papers, 1954; 213382 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Analysis of Agent's Statement- 200 Madison Ave, 213383 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Charles F. Noyes Co. Inc. Disbursement Statements, 1947; 213384 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Charles F. Noyes Co. Inc. Disbursement Statements, 1948; 213385 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Charles F. Noyes Co. Inc. Disbursement Statements, 1949; 213386 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Statement of Disbursements, 1950; 213387 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Statement of Disbursements, 1951; 213388 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Statement of Disbursements, 1952; 213389 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Statement of Disbursements, 1953; 213390 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Statement of Disbursements, 1954; 213391 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Analysis of Agent's Statement, 1953-1954; 213392 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Unemployment Insurance Reports, New York State, 1948-1953; 213393 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Bankers Trust Co., 1947; 213394 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - National City Bank- 42nd St. Brnach Branch, N.Y., 1952; 213395 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Schedules of Prepaid Expenses, 213396 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Blue Cross Hospitalization Plan and Premium Payments- 32 B Plan, 213397 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - New York (I), 1954-1964; 213398 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - New York (II), 1954-1964; 213401 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Closing File, 1954; 213404 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Various Documents, 1947-1953; 213405 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Various Documents, 1948-1961; 213406 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Various Documents, 1946-1952; 213407 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - I.I.I.I.I.I.I.I. Misc., 1954; 213408 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Various Documents, 1952; 216923 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Various Documents, 1954; 213409 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Misc Papers, 1954-1955; 213410 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Minute Book, 1947-1952; 213411 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Minute Book, 1947-1954; 213412 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Minute Book vol. 2, 1955-1958; 213413 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Stock Book, 1947; 213414 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Madison Operating Corporation, 216922
    - Ledger, 1945-1949; 213416 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Ledger Book, 1949-1955; 213417 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Manager- Operating Journal, 1949-1954; 213418 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Cash Book, 1951-1955; 217720 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Federal Tax, 1931-1940; 213419 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Franchise Tax, 1933-1955; 217719 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Federal Tax; Capital Stock Tax, 1931-1940; 1931-1955; 217722 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Federal Tax, 1941-1946; 217733 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Federal Tax, 1943-1953; 217734 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Federal Payroll + Employees Income Tax Returns (I), 1948-1955; 217735 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Federal Payroll + Employees Income Tax Returns (II), 1948-1955; 217736 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - State Unemployment + Disability Tax Return, 1949-1954; 217738 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - FOAB Quarterly Tax Returns, 1944-1947; 217739 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - work Sheets, 1949; 217741 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Work Papers, 1950; 217742 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Work Papers, 1951; 217744 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Work Papers, 1952; 218061 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Work Papers, 1953; 218062 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Work Papers, 1954; 218063 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Dissolution Return, 1/1/1955-3/14/1955; 218064 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Delaware State Report, 1929-1954; 218065 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Bank Statements, 1952-1955; 218066 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Bank Reconciliation and Bankstatements- Bankers Trust Co., 1953-1955; 218067 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Bank Statements- National City Bank- Sutton Place, 1954; 218068 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Assignment of Lease to Louis Schleifer, 1958; 218069 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Final Bills, Letters, Etc. in Connection with Dissolution, 1955-1959; 218070 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - New York Steam Co. Assignment (Deposit), 1928-1944; 218072 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Annual Information Return, Form 1096, 1951-1954; 218626 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - New York City Gross Receipts Tax, 1955; 218627 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Special Account, 1950-1955; 218628 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Payroll Data- Personnel, 1952-1954; 218630 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Employee Records, 1938-1950; 218632 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Misc., 1953-1954; 218633 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Misc. Letters, Papers, etc. in connection with closing New York office, 1955; 218634 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Stock Certificates, 1928-1955; 218728 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Main + Congress Realty Co., 218730
    - Income Tax, 1914-1916; 218731 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - H.T.D. Wilson, 1909-1912; 218732 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Change to Gulf Building Co., 1916; 218733 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Unsigned Notes, 1916; 218734 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Main and McKinney Building Co., 218735
    - Journal, 1925-1933; 218736 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Ledger, 1925-1933; 218737 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Ledger (2) (Dissolved), 3/13/1942; 218738 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Franchise Tax, 1930-1931; 1933-1938; 1941; 219624 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Minutes and Articles of Incorporation, 1926-1931; 219625 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Various Documents, 1926; 219627 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Various Documents, 1929-1953; 219628 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Stock Book, 1925-1933; 219629 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Main Properties, Inc., 219675
    - Available Income, 1935-1940; 219630 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Accounts Receivable (I), 1934-1941; 219631 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Accounts of Receivable (II), 1941-1942; 219632 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Ledger, 1934-1942; 219634 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Cash Received, 1934-1942; 219635 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Disbursements, 1934-1942; 219637 (Box 70, Folder data_value_missing_9923849f1ca5bee7d3826ca6b9c30f43)
      - Accounts Payable and Journal, 1934-1942; 219638 (Box 70, Folder data_value_missing_fe44a23b4c9d628ca47b9053d981a1b6)
    - Ledger Book (I), 1939-1941; 219655 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Ledger Book (II), 1939-1941; 219657 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Statements, 1934; 219660 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Franchise Tax, 1936-1940; 219663 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Income Tax Return, 1936; 219665 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Income Tax Return, 1936-1937; 219666 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Income Tax Return, 1937-1938; 219667 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Income Tax Return, 1938-1939; 219669 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Income Tax Return, 1939-1940; 219670 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Income Tax Return, 1941; 219671 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Dissolution Return, 1941-1942; 219672 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Minute Book, 1934-1941; 219673 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Stock Book, 1934-1937; 219674 (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Various Documents, 1934-1944; 219690 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Main and Rusk Realty Co., 219694
    - Correspondence, 1953-1955; 219695 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Majestic Realty Co., 219698
    - Income Tax, 1914-1921; 219699 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Stock Book, 1909-1922; 219701 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Various Documents, 1909-1925; 219702 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Manhatten Construction Company of Texas, 219705
    - Financial Statements, 1957-1958; 219704 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Marine Bank and Trust Co., 219708
    - Various Documents, 1933-1934; 219709 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Mason Block Realty Co., 219712
    - Available Income, 1935-1940; 219710 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Ledger, 1935-1941; 219715 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Transfer Ledger (I), 1941-1947; 219716 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Transfer Ledger (II), 1935-1941; 219717 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Ledgers, 1934-1947; 219718 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Cash Received, 1935-1945; 219719 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Cash Disbursed, 1935-1945; 219720 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Accounts Payable, 1935-1940; 219721 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1935-1947; 219722 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Ledger Book, 1941-1947; 219727 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Agency Account with Realt Management Co. Record of Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1942-1947; 219728 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Statements, 1934-1941; 219776 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Franchise Tax, 1935-1947; 219777 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax, 1928; 1935-1947; 219778 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Minute Book, 1928-1940; 219779 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Minute Book, 1942-1948; 219780 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1947-1948; 219781 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Stock Book, 1928-1935; 219782 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Stock Book, 1942_1948; 219783 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Various Documents, 1928-1948; 219784 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Mason Building Co., 219785
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1912; 219786 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Income Tax, 1913; 219787 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Various Documents, 1912-1917; 219788 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Stockholders, 1921; 219789 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Change to: Southern Loan and Investment Corp., 1929; 219790 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Mason Investment Co., 219791
    - Ledger, 1913-1951; 219792 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Ledger Book (1), 1962-1964; 219793 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Ledger Book (1), 1962-1964; 219801 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Ledger Book (2) (I), 1962-1963; 219794 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Ledger Book (2) (II), 1962-1963; 219795 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Franchise Tax, 1932-1963; 219796 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Income Tax, 1932-1939; 219797 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Income Tax, 1940-1948; 219798 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Income Tax, 1949-1964; 219799 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Liquidation into HEI, 12/31/1964; 219800 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Minute Book, 1932-1964; 219802 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Stock Book, 1932-1952; 219803 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Various Documents, 1937-1952; 219804 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - McKinney Avenue of Realty Co., 219805
    - Various Documents, 1956; 219806 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Merchant's National Bank of Houston, 219807
    - Various Documents, 1910; 219808 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Properties Corp., 219809
    - Ledger, 1932-1934; 219810 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Statements, 1926-1931; 219811 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Statements, 1927-1930; 219812 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Statements, 1929-1932; 219813 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Statements, 1931-1932; 219814 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Statements, 1934; 219815 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Income Tax, 1933; 219816 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Various Documents, 1920-1953; 219817 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Milam Properties, Inc., 219818
    - Available Income, 1936-1939; 219819 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Transfer Ledger (1) (I), 1936-1947; 219820 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Transfer Ledger (1) (II), 1936-1947; 219821 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Transfer Ledger (1) (III), 1936-1947; 219822 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Ledger, 1936-1947; 219823 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Cash Received, 1936-1947; 219824 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Cash Disbursement, 1936-1947; 219825 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Accounts Payable and Journal Entries, 1936-1947; 219826 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Cancelled Notes, 1936-1944; 219827 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Statements, 1936-1937; 219828 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Franchise Tax, 1937-1946; 219829 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Income Tax, 1936-1947; 219830 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Minute Book, 1936-1947; 219831 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Stock Book, 1936-1947; 219832 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Transfer to Houston Industries, Inc., 9/30/1947; 219833 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Various Documents, 1936-1947; 219834 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Milum and Rusk Building, Co., 219835
    - Income Tax Return, 1932-1936; 219836 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Minute Book, 1931-1936; 219837 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Monterey Lumber + Manufacturing Co., 219838
    - Various Documents, 1895-1922; 219839 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - The National Bank of Commerce, 219840
    - Bankers Blanket Bonds, 1944-1947; 219841 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Bankers Blanket Bonds, 1950-1957; 219842 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Bankers Blanket Bonds, 1958-1964; 219843 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Brochure, 1960; 219844 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - R.S. Coon Resolution, 1941; 219845 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Lease: South Texas Commercial National Bank, 1912-1915; 219846 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Lease: Langham and Maillot Gulf Building, 1932; 219847 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1954-1959; 219848 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - R. Sterling- $800,000 Loan, 1931-1932; 219849 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - R. Sterling- $800,000 Loan, 1931-1932; 219850 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Public National Bank, 1931; 219851 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Stock Options, 1958-1963; 219852 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Texas State Bank of Houston- Stock Purchase, 1956; 219853 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Stock Sale to G. H. Jewell, 1964-1965; 219854 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Stock Holders, 1921-1922; 219855 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - MacGregor Park National Bank; Regan State Bank; Adline State Bank; Northside State Bank; Fairbanks State Bank, 1953-1981; 219857 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Reagan State Bank: Statements and City Deposits, 1950-1968; 219860 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Reagan State Bank: Daily Balance Sheets, 1968; 219861 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Samtaub Agreement, 1921; 219862 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Various Documents, 1928-1959; 219863 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Various Documents, 1948-1957; 219864 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Various Documents, 1956; 219865 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1959; 219866 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1964-1968; 219867 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1968; 219869 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1968; 219870 (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1968; 219868 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1968; 219871 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1968; 219872 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Texas National Bank of Commerce Stock Sale to American General Insurance Co., 1968; 219904 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Texas Commerce Bank Merger with Chemical New York Bank, 1986-1987; 219906 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Texas Commerce Bank Merger with Chemical New York Bank, 1987; 219907 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Texas Commerce Bank Merger with Chemical New York Bank, 1987; 219908 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - National City Bank of Houston, 223203
    - Various Documents, 1908; 219909 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Varous Documents, 1909; 219910 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Various Documents, 1909-1914; 219919 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - National Properties Corp., 223225
    - Journal and Cash Book, 1940-1955; 219911 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - National Properties Corp. Journal and Cash Book, 1940-1955; 219939 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Minute Book (I), 1929-1955; 219938 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Minute Book (II), 1929 - 1955; 219941 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Stock Book, 1932-1946; 219942 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1929; 219943 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Various Documents, 219944 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Neece and Meador Lumber Company, 223241
    - Neece and Meador Lumber Co, Various Documents, 1904; 219952 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - New Rice Hotel, 223242
    - First Draft - First Meeting, 1911; 219956 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Nine Hundred Main, Inc., 223228
    - Income and Expenses, 1938 - 1945; 219957 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - (No. 1) Assets and Liabilities, 1938 - 1945; 219958 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Ledgers, 1938-1945; 219959 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Cash Received, 1938-1945; 223243 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Disbursements, 1938-1945; 223244 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Accounts Payable; Journal, 1938-1945; 223245 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Cash Received; Disbursements; Accounts Payable; Journal, 1945; 223246 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Franchise Tax, 1938 - 1944; 219960 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Income Tax, 219961; 1938-1945 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Loan, 1940; 219962 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Loan, 1941; 219963 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Stock Book, 1938 -1945; 219964 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Various Documents, 1939 - 1941; 219965 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Various Documents, 1928 - 1950; 219966 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Nine Hundred Main Inc., Various Documents, 1928 - 1950; 219970 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Nine Hundred Main Inc., Various Documents, 1938-1945; 219976 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - The North Field Co., 223247
    - Journal; Cash Receipts; Cash Disbursements, 1946-1947; 219972 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Franchise Tax, 1930-1963; 219980 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax, 1914-1931; 219981 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Income Tax, 1934-1939; 219982 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Income Tax, 1940-1962; 219983 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Loan - BL80 Lots 1,2,3 (Texas State Hotel), 1926-1945; 219986 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Minute Book Vol.1, 219989 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Minute Book Vol.II, 219990 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Stock Book, 1947-; 219991 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Various Documents, 1914 - 1946; 219992 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Orange Lumber Co., 223248
    - Various Documents, 1903-1905; 219993 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Various Documents, 1906; 219994 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Log Scale Bills, 1906; 219995 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Various Documents, 1907; 219996 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Various Documents, 1908-1913; 219997 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Osteopathic Hospital and Clinic, 223249
    - Closing Statements, 1954; 219998 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Palestine Lumber Co., 223250
    - Various Documents, 1909; 219999 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Park Ave - 65th Street Corporation., 223227
    - Bank Resolutions, 1964-1967; 220000 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Statements, 1949 - 1954; 220001 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - New York State Franchise Tax, 220004 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Federal Tax Returns, 1949 - 1953; 220007 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Income Tax, 1949 - 1963; 220010 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Income Tax, 1964-1971; 220011 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - New York State Corporation Tax, General Corp. Year, Begin. 1949 - 1966; 220012 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Re: Sale, 1972; 220013 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Current File on Mayfair House Real Estate Taxes and Protests of Assessments, etc., 1969-1977; 220014 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Receipted Real Estate Tax Bills - 610-12 Park Ave Property (I), 1933-1967; 220017 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Receipted Real Estate Tax Bills - 610-12 Park Ave Properties (II), 220018 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Various Documents, 1969 - 1973; 220020 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Mayfair House, 223226
    - Park 65th Street Corp., Depreciation, 1950-1955; 220024 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Park 65th Street Corp., Depreciation, 1956-1958; 223251 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Mr. la Belle, Miscellaneous Correspondence, etc., 1955; 220027 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Capital Expendiutres, 1959; 220028 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Capital Expendiutres, 1960; 220320 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Capital Expendiutres, 1961; 220321 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Capital Expendiutres, 1962; 220322 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Cocktail Lounge and Small Dining Room, 1962; 220323 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Remodeling Cocktail Lounge and Dining Room, Statements, etc., 1962; 220332 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1963; 220334 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Capital Expenditures (I), 1964; 220335 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Capital Expenditures (II), 1964; 220336 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Capital Expenditures (III), 1964; 220337 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Capital Expenditures; Sundry Items Paid, 1965; 220338 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Capital Expenditures; Sundry Items Paid, 1966; 223252 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1967; 223253 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Capital Expenditures- New York, 1968; 223254 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1969; 220015 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1970; 223255 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1971; 223256 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Finchbach and Moore, 1969; 223257 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Peer Properties, Inc, 223258
    - Ledger, 1939-1941; 223259 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Transfer Ledger, 1942-1945; 223260 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Ledger, 1942-1945; 223261 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Cash Received; Disbursements; Accounts Payable; Journal; Bank Statements, 1942-1945; 223283 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Franchise Tax, 1940-1945; 223262 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Income Tax, 1939-1944; 223263 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Loan- Electric Building (BL 137), 1933-1946; 223264 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Loan- Electric Building (BL 137), 1942; 223265 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Minute Book, 1939-1945; 223266 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Stock Book, 1939-1945; 223267 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Various Documents, 1942-1945; 223268 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Phoenix Corp., 223275
    - Assets, 1939-1964; 223276 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Liabilities and Income, 1939-1964; 223277 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Expenses, 1939-1964; 223278 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Ledgers, 1939-1964; 223279 (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - Cash Receipts, 1939-1964; 223284 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Cash Disbursements, 1939-1952; 223285 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Cash Disbursements, 1952-1964; 223297 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Vouchers Payable (# 2 Transfer), 1939-1961; 223298 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Journal Entries, 1939-1963; 223327 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Franchise Tax, 1939-1963; 223280 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Income Tax, 1939-1951; 223281 (Box 80, Folder 20)